{
    "subject": "resource/Josh_Homme",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/Eagles_of_Death_Metal",
    "human_readable": "Josh Homme is associated with Eagles of Death Metal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9839473962783813,
            "question": "Is Josh Homme a member of Eagles of Death Metal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9525856971740723,
            "question": "How long has Josh Homme been associated with Eagles of Death Metal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9336799383163452,
            "question": "Besides Eagles of Death Metal, what other bands is Josh Homme involved with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9219716787338257,
            "question": "Has Josh Homme released music outside of Eagles of Death Metal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7612238526344299,
            "question": "Who is Josh Homme associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4212524890899658,
            "question": "What genre of music does Eagles of Death Metal play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1972332000732422,
            "question": "What instruments does Josh Homme play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16833218932151794,
            "question": "What musical group is Josh Homme known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1361793577671051,
            "question": "What is the name of Josh Homme's solo project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11647872626781464,
            "question": "What is the name of Josh Homme's most famous band?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Josh Homme is associated with Eagles of Death Metal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7867_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Josh Homme's solo project?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7867_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical group is Josh Homme known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7867_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments does Josh Homme play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7867_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7867_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the context information provided, which clearly mentions that \"Eagles of Death Metal is an American rock band from Palm Desert, California, formed in 1998 by best friends Jesse Hughes and Josh Homme.\" This supports the statement that Josh Homme is associated with Eagles of Death Metal."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}